in this tutorial we'll be going over
在本教程中，我们将复习
everything you need to know about
你需要知道的一切
drawing lines in inkscape so getting us
在Inkscape中绘制线条，这样我们就可以
started let's first go over how you can
开始，让我们先来了解一下如何
draw simple straight lines to do that
画一条简单的直线来做这件事
we're going to use the pencil tool which
我们要用铅笔工具
could be located over here in your
可能在你的房间里
toolbar or you can access it by pressing
工具栏，或者您可以通过按
the letter P on your
你身上的字母P
keyboard when you have the pencil tool
当您有铅笔工具时使用键盘
enabled you'll notice up here in the
启用后，您会注意到上面的
tool settings we have these three
工具设置我们有这三个
different modes that we can work with
我们可以使用的不同模式
these are the different types of lines
这些是不同类型的线路
that you can draw and in this lesson
在这一课中，你可以画出
we'll be going over all three but let's
我们会把这三个都复习一遍，但让我们
first focus on this setting right here
首先关注这里的设置
which allows us to draw simple straight
这让我们可以简单直接地画出
lines so to draw your straight line all
线条，画出你所有的直线
you have to do is Click once to add a
您只需单击一次即可添加一个
point and then move your cursor wherever
指向并将光标移动到任意位置
you would like the line to be and then
你希望线路是这样的，然后
click again to add another point and now
再次单击以添加另一个点，现在
we have a simple two-point line as you
我们和你一样有一条简单的两点线
can see there if you want to continue
如果您想继续，可以在那里看到
drawing this line all you have to do is
划出这条线你所要做的就是
connect back to one of these nodes and
连接回其中一个节点，然后
click move your cursor wherever you
单击将光标移动到任何位置
would like the next line to be placed
我想把下一行放在
and click again and now we have a single
再次点击，现在我们有了一首单曲
three-point line that follows a Bend
折弯后的三点线
here so let's say you want to draw
在这里，假设你想画
straight lines that follow a perfect
紧跟在完美之后的直线
vertical or horizontal path all you have
您拥有的所有垂直或水平路径
to do is click to add your point and
要做的就是点击添加您的观点并
then while placing your line hold the
然后，在放置线条的同时按住
control key on your keyboard and if you
键盘上的Ctrl键，如果您
bring your cursor down and up you get a
将光标向下和向上移动即可得到一个
perfectly vertical line or if you bring
完美的垂直线或者如果你带着
it left and right you get a perfectly
它向左和向右，你得到一个完美的
horizontal line and you can rotate it
水平线，你可以旋转它
around like this to place your line in
像这样绕来绕去，把线放进去
15° increments so I'm going to create a
15°的增量，所以我要创建一个
vertical line right here click to add
垂直线条在此处单击可添加
the point and I'm going to continue
这一点，我将继续
drawing straight lines down here I'm
在这里画直线，我在这里
going to hold I'm going to hold control
我要坚持，我要坚持控制
and draw a horizontal line now and then
时不时地画一条水平线
I will draw one more line up here back
我会在后面再画一条线
to the starting point and we end up with
到起点，我们最终会得到
something like that right there so let
类似的东西就在那里，所以让
me get rid of that and show you what
我把它扔掉，然后让你看看
else this Bode can do so going back to
否则这只波德就可以回到
the pencil tool another thing you can do
铅笔工具另一件你可以做的事情
with this tool is draw freehand lines so
用这个工具可以画出手绘的线条
if I click and drag like that you'll
如果我像那样点击并拖动，你会
notice we get a scribbled line that
请注意，我们得到了一条潦草的线条
follows my hand movement so this would
跟随我的手的移动，所以这会
be useful if you're creating something
如果你在创造一些东西，那就有用了
like a signature or maybe if you're
就像签名，或者如果你是
using a stylus or a pen and you're want
使用触控笔或钢笔，你想要
and you want to draw calligraphy or
你想画书法还是
something like that that would be a good
像那样的东西将是一个很好的
mode to use for that the problem with
用于解决该问题的模式
using this pen mode though is that it's
不过，使用这种笔模式是因为它
hard to get really smooth lines so let's
很难得到真正流畅的线条，所以让我们
say I wanted to draw a curse of letter L
说我想画L的咒语
like that this does not look very fluid
像这样，这看起来不是很流畅
because it follows my hand movement and
因为它跟随着我的手的动作
my hand isn't perfectly stable so this
我的手不太稳，所以这个
is where these other pen modes come in
就是这些其他笔模式的用武之地
handy I'm going to click on the Spyro
汉迪，我要点击Spyro
option now this middle option right here
选项现在这个中间选项就在这里
that says create spiral path this makes
上面写着创建螺旋路径
it so that the freehand lines you draw
这样你画出的写意线条
follow a much more fluid Contour so if I
遵循更流畅的轮廓，所以如果我
were to draw that same letter L over
把同一封信L画过来
here I get a different output over here
我在这里得到了不同的输出
it looks much more smooth in fluid now
现在在液体中看起来光滑多了
to show you what I mean even more let me
为了让你知道我的意思更让我
change the size of this so we can see
更改这个的大小，这样我们就可以看到
this line better and I'll do the same
这条线更好，我也会这么做的
thing to this line over here I'll make
把东西放到这条线上，我会做的
this bigger as well I'm going to change
这个也更大，我要换衣服了
the stroke size to
的笔划大小
seven now I'm going to select this line
现在我要选择这条线
right here and I'm going to grab the
就在这里，我要拿起
nodes tool and if you know notice the
Nodes工具，如果您知道，请注意
blue path on there represents the line
那里的蓝色路径表示这条线
that I drew but the black line
我画的只是那条黑线
represents smooth path that was created
表示创建的平滑路径
so if I move these nodes around I can
因此，如果我移动这些节点，我可以
change the Contour of the line but it
更改直线的轮廓，但它
stays smooth the whole time it never
从头到尾都保持平稳
it's never not smooth it remains pretty
它永远不会不平坦，它仍然美丽
fluid as you can see there so that isn't
就像你在那里看到的一样，所以这不是
exactly the case over here if I click on
如果我点击这里，情况就是这样
these handles over here you don't really
这里的这些把手你并不是真的
get that smoothness maintained you have
保持你所拥有的顺畅
more control from these handles this is
更多来自这些手柄的控制，这是
better for creating accurate lines but
更适合创建精确的线条，但是
this is better over here for creating
这个更适合在这里创作
really smooth
真的很顺利
lines so let's go over that final option
台词，让我们来看看最后一个选项
now I'm going to go back to the let me
现在我要回到《让我来》
deselect everything and go back to the
取消选择所有内容并返回到
pencil tool and we have this final
铅笔工具，我们有这个期末考试
option over here which is creating Beast
此处的选项是创建Beast
blind paths now this is more useful when
盲道现在，这在以下情况下更有用
it comes to using the bezier pen which
说到使用贝塞尔钢笔，它
we'll go over in just a minute but this
我们一会儿就过去，但是这个
does work with the pencil as well so let
用铅笔也行，所以让我们
me show you how this works this also
我来给你演示一下这是怎么回事
allows you to draw smooth lines but it
允许您绘制流畅的线条，但它
gives you more control over the nodes
使您能够更好地控制节点
afterwards so if I change the size of
之后，所以如果我更改了
this let me make this seven again I can
这让我再次成为七人组我能做到
come over here to the nodes tool and if
到这里来使用节点工具，如果
you notice we have this path that we can
你注意到我们有这条路，我们可以
edit but the lines are drawn using
编辑，但线条是使用
straight lines for the path and then the
路径的直线，然后是
actual stroke itself follows a curved
实际的笔划本身遵循一条曲线
line so this the trade-off you're making
所以这就是你要做的权衡
here this is not as fluid as this option
在这里，这不像这个选项那样灵活
over here but this option over here
在这里，但这个选项在这里
gives you more control over where
让您可以更好地控制
exactly you can place the Contours of
准确地说，你可以把它的轮廓
the line This option over here gives you
这个选项在这里为您提供的线路
smoother lines but it's kind of hard to
线条更流畅，但很难
really control where the lines get
真正控制着线条的位置
placed because it's always making sure
放置是因为它总是确保
that the lines were made smooth now
这些线条现在已经变得光滑了
let's go over how you can draw lines
让我们来看看你是如何绘制线条的
using the be pen which is located over
使用位于上方的BE笔
here in your toolbar or you can access
在您的工具栏中，或者您可以访问
it by pressing the letter B on your
将字母B按在您的计算机上即可
keyboard and when you have this tool
键盘和当你有这个工具的时候
enabled up here in the tool settings you
在您的工具设置中启用此处
notice we have the three same settings
请注意，我们有三个相同的设置
that we had previously in the pencil
我们之前在铅笔里看到的
tool in addition to these other two so
工具，以及其他两个SO
let's go over what all of this does Now
让我们来回顾一下这一切现在的作用
to create straight lines with the bezi
用贝兹创造直线
pen all you have to do is click to add a
笔您只需单击即可添加一个
point just like the PC tool but the
与PC工具类似的点，但
difference is that as you add points the
不同的是，当您将点添加到
line does not end the line goes on as
行不会结束，行仍在继续
long as you'd like it to go on so this
只要你想让它继续下去就这样
is ideal for drawing one long continuous
非常适合绘制一个长的连续的
line as you can see there and this line
你可以看到这条线和这条线
does not end until you either connect
不会结束，直到您连接
back to the starting point or you press
返回起始点或按
enter on the keyboard to end the path
按键盘上的Enter键结束路径
like that and another thing that you can
就像这样，还有一件你能做的事
do with this mode is you can also draw
用这种模式做的就是你也可以画
curved lines in addition to the straight
直线之外的曲线
lines so if I were to draw a straight
所以如果我要画一条直线
line like this and make it vertical and
像这样划一条线，然后把它竖直
click to add my point I can come up here
点击添加我的观点，我可以在这里找到
and I can click and drag to add my point
我可以点击并拖动来添加我的观点
and as I'm clicking and dragging it
当我点击并拖动它时
curves the line as you can see there and
如你所见，这条线是弯曲的
then you could bring the other side down
然后你就可以把另一边搞垮
like this over here bring this line
像这样，把这条线拿过来
straight down and connect it back to the
往下直走，然后把它连接回
starting point and now we end up with
起点，现在我们以
this Pac-Man sort of shape right here
这个吃豆人的形状就在这里
now the problem with drawing curved
现在，绘制曲线的问题是
lines in this method is that there's a
此方法中的代码行是有一个
pretty steep learning curve with this
这是一个相当陡峭的学习曲线
sort of method it's really hard to
一种方法，真的很难
create accurate lines that follow the
创建符合以下条件的精确线条
the Contour that you want so this is
你想要的等高线，所以这是
where these other modes come in handy so
在这些其他模式派上用场的地方
let me get rid of all of this
让我把这一切都处理掉
here and I'm going to choose the spiral
在这里，我将选择螺旋线
path now now if I click to add my points
如果我点击添加我的点数，现在就可以选择路径
it's creating an automatic spiral path
它正在创造一条自动的螺旋路径
as you can see there and if I draw My
正如你所看到的，如果我画出我的
Curse of letter L that I tried with the
我试着用的字母L的诅咒
pencil tool earlier I end up with a much
铅笔工具早些时候我得到了一个
better result here because this allows
这里的结果更好，因为这允许
me to create more accurate placements of
我要创建更准确的位置
where the line is clicking and dragging
线条正在单击和拖动的位置
is always less accurate than clicking to
的精确度总是不如单击
add individual points and you can see
添加单独的点，您可以看到
here we end up with a much better result
在这里，我们最终得到了一个更好的结果
so let me make this
所以让我来做这件事
bigger I'm able to get the proportions
更大的，我可以得到比例
just how I like
就像我喜欢的那样
it and if I grab my nodes tool you'll
如果我拿起我的节点工具，你会
notice we have these editable nodes here
请注意，我们这里有这些可编辑的节点
the path remains smooth no matter what I
无论我做什么，道路都是平坦的
do to
做收件人
it and then finally over here we have
它，然后最后在这里我们有
let me go back to the pen tool over here
让我回到这里的钢笔工具
up top we have the be lines this works
在顶端，我们有BE行，这行得通
the same way we're clicking to add
就像我们点击添加
points and it's creating a curved line
点，它创造了一条曲线
although we're drawing a straight path
尽管我们画的是一条笔直的道路
we're drawing straight lines indicated
我们画的是直线
by the Blue Line there and then the path
在那里的蓝线，然后是小路
being
存在
drawn is curved so I can press enter
绘制的是曲线，所以我可以按Enter键
like that and the downside with this is
就像这样，这样做的缺点是
that the path isn't as smooth but the N
这条路并不平坦，但N
the nodes are easier to control same
节点更易于控制
with the pencil tool it just gives you
使用铅笔工具，它只会给你
more control over these nodes here like
对这些节点的更多控制，如
that let me make this bigger so you can
让我把它做得更大，这样你就可以
see it
看到了吗？
better and there you go now another
更好了，现在你又来了一个
thing that you should keep in mind when
在以下情况下应牢记的事情
using this mode this is actually one of
使用此模式，这实际上是
the best modes to use with the pen tool
与钢笔工具配合使用的最佳模式
I use this more than anything because
我用这个比什么都多，因为
not only can you draw curved lines
你不仅能画出曲线
easily you can also create straight
您还可以轻松地创建直线
lines as well if you hold the shift key
如果按住Shift键，也可以使用线条
so I'm going to hold shift and click to
所以我要按住Shift键并单击以
add a point and now we have a corner
再加一分，我们就有了一个拐角
node there and if I hold shift again and
节点在那里，如果我再次按住Shift键
control I can draw a straight line like
控件，我可以像这样画一条直线
that and now we have a combination of
现在我们有了一个组合
straight lines and curved lines as you
直线和曲线就像你
can see there and this is actually the
可以在那里看到，这实际上是
tool that I use whenever I'm tracing a
每当我跟踪一个
subject to create a silhouette or
以创造一个剪影或
something like that I'll put a uh a
类似的东西，我会放一个呃一个
little video up on the screen here so
屏幕上有一段视频，所以
you can see what I mean this allows you
你可以明白我的意思，这让你
to create nice smooth fluid lines that
要创建流畅流畅的线条，
follow what you're tracing accurately
准确地跟踪您要跟踪的内容
while also allowing you to create
同时还允许您创建
straight lines to go with it so let me
直线来搭配吧，所以让我
get rid of all this and let's go over
把这些都扔掉，让我们再来一遍
these final two modes right here this
这最后两个模式就在这里
one right here is for creating only
这里有一个仅用于创作
straight lines so if I select this pen
直线所以如果我选择这支笔
mode right here it's only going to draw
模式就在这里，它只会抽签
straight lines now you may be wondering
直线现在你可能想知道
what the point of this mode is because
这种模式的意义是因为
the original pen mode lets you draw
原始画笔模式允许您绘制
straight lines as well well the
直线以及
difference is that with this tool you
不同的是，有了这个工具，您
can't accidentally draw curved lines so
不能不小心画出曲线
if I click and drag it's not going to
如果我点击并拖动它，它不会
draw curved line it's always going to be
画一条曲线，它将永远是
a straight line as you can see there now
你现在可以看到的一条直线
if I go back to my original pen mode and
如果我回到原来的笔模式，
I click like that if you click ever so
如果你这样点击，我就会这样点击
slightly you end up with a very slight
稍微一点，你就会得到一个非常轻微的
Bend in that line there even if you
在那条线上弯一弯，即使你
can't see it it's there and you could
看不到它，它就在那里，你可以
see by the handles if there's a handle
从把手看有没有把手
showing there you'll notice it's a
在那里展示，你会注意到这是一个
curved line so this is actually a
曲线所以这实际上是一条
problem when you're trying to draw
当你试着画画的时候有个问题
straight lines with this pen mode
此笔模式下的直线
sometimes you'll accidentally create a
有时，您会意外地创建一个
curved line without realizing it when
曲线在没有意识到的时候
you really need a straight line so this
你真的需要一条直线，所以这
is when this mode up here comes in handy
当这个模式在这里派上用场的时候
and then finally we have this setting up
最后，我们把这个设置好了
here which is for drawing parallel lines
这是用来画平行线的
so if I if I choose this option and
所以如果我选择了这个选项
start drawing my lines you'll notice
开始画我的线，你会注意到的
every line that I draw goes parallel to
我画的每一条线都与
the original line that I drew so this
我原来画的这条线是这样的
could be really useful if you're doing
如果你正在做的事情会非常有用
something like drawing a floor plan or
比如画一张平面图或
tracing over something that where you
追查你所在的地方
need to keep the angles preserved just
需要保持角度不变
like that and you can connect it back to
就像这样，你可以把它连接回
the starting point as you can see there
就像你在那里看到的起点
if I start off drawing a perfectly
如果我开始画一个完美的
horizontal line it's going to make it so
水平线它会让它变成这样的
that every line that I draw is vertical
我画的每一条线都是垂直的
and horizontal like that so this could
像这样水平，所以这可以
actually be really useful if you're
实际上非常有用，如果你是
doing something like tracing over a
做一些事情，比如跟踪
Skyline and you want to create like
天际线，你想要创建这样的
buildings like that it ensures that you
像这样的建筑可以确保你
never draw any kind of curved path at
永远不要在
all so those are all of the ways in
所有这些都是所有的方式
which you can go about drawing lines in
你可以在其中画线
inkscape if you found this lesson useful
如果您发现本课有用，inkscape
then consider checking out my inkscape
然后考虑检查我的水墨景观
master class it's a collection of over
大师班这是一个集合
60 videos where I go over all of the
60个视频，我回顾了所有
tools and features in inkscape and I
inkscape和I中的工具和功能
explain what they are and demonstrate
解释它们是什么并演示
how they work kind of like how I did in
他们的工作方式有点像我在
this video we even have a private
这个视频我们甚至有一个私人视频
Community where you can ask questions
您可以提问的社区
and get help from me anytime you want
并随时从我这里获得帮助
and best of all there's no monthly
最重要的是没有每月
membership fees you just pay $17 one
会员费只需支付17美元一个
time and you're in for Life I'll have
时间，你将迎来我将拥有的生活
some information about that down below
下面有一些相关信息
if you want to check that out as always
如果您想一如既往地检查一下
thanks for watching
感谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]